readforgreed.com 2015-03-15

# Privacy Policy - Read for Greed!

readforgreed.com take your privacy seriously. This policy describes what personal information we collect and how we use it. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**Routine Information Collection**  
All web servers track basic information about their visitors. This information includes, but is not limited to, IP addresses, browser details, timestamps and referring pages. None of this information can personally identify specific visitors to this site. The information is tracked for routine administration and maintenance purposes, and lets me know what pages and information are useful and helpful to visitors.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
Where necessary, this site uses cookies to store information about a visitor’s preferences and history in order to better serve the visitor and/or present the visitor with customized content.  
Advertising partners and other third parties may also use cookies, scripts and/or web beacons to track visitors to our site in order to display advertisements and other useful information. Such tracking is done directly by the third parties through their own servers and is subject to their own privacy policies.

**Controlling Your Privacy**  
Note that you can change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have privacy concerns. Disabling cookies for all sites is not recommended as it may interfere with your use of some sites. The best option is to disable or enable cookies on a per-site basis. Consult your browser documentation for instructions on how to block cookies and other tracking mechanisms.

**Special Note About Google Advertising**  
Any advertisements served by Google, Inc., and affiliated companies may be controlled using cookies. These cookies allow Google to display ads based on your visits to this site and other sites that use Google advertising services. Learn how to opt out of Google’s cookie usage. As mentioned above, any tracking done by Google through cookies and other mechanisms is subject to Google’s own privacy policies.  
About Google advertising: What is the DoubleClick DART cookie? The DoubleClick DART cookie is used by Google in the ads served on publisher websites displaying AdSense for content ads. When users visit an AdSense publisher’s website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user’s browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help AdSense publishers better serve and manage the ads on their site(s) and across the web.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Email Addresses**  
When you make a comment or contact us using the contact page your email is required. Please be assured that you email address will only be used for responding to your email or comment and will never be made publicly available. Your email address will never be sold or given away to anyone else.

**Comments Policy**  
The author does not assume responsibility over comments he did not make on this blog. While comments are welcome from anybody, we reserve the right to remove any comment that is not deemed suitable for publication. This could include but not limited to objectional and abusive comments. Hate, racist comments, or any other form of prejudice will be removed and the poster will be banned! Spam in any form will not be accepted and will be deleted immediately.

**Registering on Forum**

If you register at our website (or subdomains) or its forum, you’re agreed to our Terms & Conditions, Disclaimer and to provide correct information about you with all valid email id and other details. If we found any wrong or misleading information about any user, we may delete or ban permanently, ban IP address or can restrict to post. We may use your email ids and other informations to send you emails about promotions, offers etc. We’ll never sell your information to third party and we take it to only our use.

**Links to third party Websites**  
We have included lots of links on this site for your use and better reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**  
The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.

**Contact Information**  
Concerns or questions about this privacy policy can be directed to site admin: admin @ readforgreed.com for further clarification or can use [contact page](http://www.readforgreed.com/contact-us/ "Click Here").

(This privacy policy is applicable to all websites falling under the primary holder readforgreed.com)

* * *

**What People Searching For:** www readforgreed com
